[
  {
    "question": "David Beckham scored 85 goals. How many of his tally were free-kicks?",
    "category": "Player",
    "optiona": "14",
    "optionb": "20",
    "optionc": "26",
    "optiond": "30",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marcus Rashford open his goal scoring account in which year",
    "category": "Player",
    "optiona": "2015",
    "optionb": "2016",
    "optionc": "2017",
    "optiond": "2018",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player has made the most appearances for United?",
    "category": "Player",
    "optiona": "Ryan Giggs",
    "optionb": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
    "optionc": "Gary Neville",
    "optiond": "Bill Foulkes",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "a"
  },

  {
    "question": "How many league titles have Man Utd won?",
    "category": "Team",
    "optiona": "13",
    "optionb": "17",
    "optionc": "20",
    "optiond": "23",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "c"
  },

  {
    "question": "Manchester United were formed as Newton Heath in which year?",
    "category": "Team",
    "optiona": "1864",
    "optionb": "1878",
    "optionc": "1890",
    "optiond": "1900",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who did Wayne Rooney surpass to become Man Utd’s all-time top scorer?",
    "category": "Player",
    "optiona": "Denis Law",
    "optionb": "George Best",
    "optionc": "Jack Rowley",
    "optiond": "Sir Bob Charlton",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team did United beat to win the 1968 European Cup final?",
    "optiona": "Benfica",
    "optionb": "Juventus",
    "optionc": "Real Madrid",
    "optiond": "Saint-Etienne",
    "category": "Competition",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "a"
  },

  {
    "question": "Who scored Man Utd’s two goals in the 1999 Champions League final?",
    "optiona": "Beckham and Solskjaer",
    "optionb": "Giggs and Sheringham",
    "optionc": "Yorke and Cole",
    "optiond": "Solshjaer and Sheringham",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "category": "Competition",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much did Cristiano Ronaldo cost Man Utd in 2003?",
    "optiona": "£8 million",
    "optionb": "£10 million",
    "optionc": "£12 million",
    "optiond": "£14 million",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "category": "Player",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored United’s winning goal vs Liverpool in the 1996 FA Cup final?",
    "optiona": "David Beckam",
    "optionb": "Paul Scholes",
    "optionc": "Gary Pallister",
    "optiond": "Eric Cantona",
    "category": "Competition",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who scored Man Utd’s two goals in the 1999 Champions League final?",
    "optiona": "Beckham and Solskjaer",
    "optionb": "Giggs and Sheringham",
    "optionc": "Yorke and Cole",
    "optiond": "Solshjaer and Sheringham",
    "category": "Competition",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "category": "Team",
    "question": "Which two Premier League sides have Man Utd beaten 9-0?",
    "optiona": "Ipswich Town and Southampton",
    "optionb": "Ipswich Town and Nottingham Forest",
    "optionc": "Blackburn Rovers and Nottingham Forest",
    "optiond": "Debry County and Southampton",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of United’s mascot?",
    "category": "Team",
    "optiona": "Fred the Red",
    "optionb": "Dave the Devil",
    "optionc": "Stretford Ender",
    "optiond": "Red Devil",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Man Utd lift the European Cup for the third time in 2008?",
    "category": "Competitions",
    "optiona": "Turin",
    "optionb": "Barcelona",
    "optionc": "Moscow",
    "optiond": "Munich",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "c"
  },

  {
    "question": "Man Utd's last Premier League title came in which season?",
    "category": "Team",
    "optiona": "2009-10",
    "optionb": "2010-11",
    "optionc": "2011-12",
    "optiond": "2012-13",
    "correctanswer": "Benfica",
    "answer": "d"
  }
]
